[
    {
        "title" : "TV and Entertainment"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which series became Netflix's biggest ever show in September 2021?",
      "answer": "Squid Game"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which girl group performed during the opening minutes of Channel 5's launch in 1997 in the UK?",
        "answer": "The Spice Girls"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In what year did Coronation Street first air on ITV?",
        "answer": "1960"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the highest-rated TV series on the IMDB Top 250 TV series list?",
        "answer": "Breaking Bad"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which British TV show recorded the largest audience for a single episode with over 30 million viewers?",
        "answer": "Eastenders (Christmas Day 1986)"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Who does the voiceover on Love Island?",
        "answer": "Iain Stirling"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "In 1995, more than 22 million people tuned into a special BBC Panorama interview with Princess Diana. Which journalist conducted the interview?",
        "answer": "Martin Bashir"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What colour is Thunderbird 2 piloted by Virgil Tracy in Thunderbirds?",
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Ant and Dec first worked together on which children's TV drama?",
        "answer": "Biker Grove"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which singing competition was the first to feature Simon Cowell as a judge?",
        "answer": "Pop Idol"
    }
]
